Prints and Printing Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Prints. (Box 3)
  - Non-Asian., 3275 (Box 7)
    - Germany., 602 (Box 22)
      - Known artists., 539 (Box 23)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 109 (Box 23)
          - Menzel, Adolf, 1815-1905., 1 (Box 24)
          - Muller, Otto, 1874-1930., 2 (Box 24)
          - Nebel, Otto, 1892-., 2 (Box 24)
          - Olivier, J. H. Ferdinand van, 1785-1841., 1 (Box 24)
          - Ostendorfer, Michael, c.1490-1559., 1 (Box 24)
          - Pankok, Otto, 1893-., 1 (Box 24)
          - Penck, A. R., 1939-., 1 (Box 24)
          - Pencz, Geore, 1500-1550., 1 (Box 24)
          - Preller, Friedrich, 1804-1878., 1 (Box 24)
          - Pruss, Johann, after 1490., 1 (Box 24)
          - Quinta, Claudia, c.1473., 1 (Box 24)
          - Rebhan, Dominik, XX C., 1 (Box 24)
          - Reger, Johann, active 1490., 1 (Box 24)
          - Reinhart, Johann Christian, 1761-1847., 1 (Box 24)
          - Rethel, Alfred, 1816-1859., 1 (Box 24)
          - Rohlfs, Christian, 1849-1938., 1 (Box 24)
          - Rupert (Prince Rupert of the Rhine), 1619-1682., 2 (Box 24)
          - Sattler, Josef, 1867-1931., 1 (Box 24)
          - Schauffelin, Hans Leonard, c.1490-c.1539., 2 (Box 24)
          - Schoen, Erhard, -1542., 1 (Box 24)
          - Schonsperger, Johann, active 1498., 1 (Box 24)
          - Schott, Martin, active 1490., 1 (Box 24)
          - Solis, Virgil, 1514-1562., 1 (Box 24)
          - Steinhardt, Jakob, 1887-., 2 (Box 24)
          - Stoss, Veit, 1440-1533., 1 (Box 24)
          - Van Meckenem, I., 1450-1503/1517., 1 (Box 24)
          - Von Ripper, C., XX C., 1 (Box 24)
          - Van Schwind, Moritz, 1804-1871., 1 (Box 24)
          - Wahlstedt, Walther, 1898-., 1 (Box 24)
          - Weiditz, Hans, active 1516-1536., 1 (Box 24)
          - Weiss, Ernest Rudolf, 1875-., 1 (Box 24)
          - Wolffgang, Johann Georg, 1664-1748., 1 (Box 24)
          - Wunderlich, Paul, 1927-., 2 (Box 24)
          - Ysenhut, Leinhart, active c.1490., 1 (Box 24)
        - Individual artists, A-Z., 430 (Box 24)
          - Aldegrever, Heinrich, 1502-1558., 14 (Box 24)
          - Altdorfer, Albrecht, 1480-1538., 38 (Box 25)
          - Baldung, Hans (Grien), 1480-1545., 9 (Box 25)
          - Barlach, Ernst, 1870-1938., 5 (Box 25)
          - Beckmann, Max, 1884-1950., 5 (Box 25)
          - Burgkmair, Hans, 1473-1531., 14 (Box 25)
          - Campendonk, Heinrich, 1889-1957., 5 (Box 25)
          - Cranach, Lucas, 1472-1553., 21 (Box 25)
          - Dix, Otto, 1891-1969., 8 (Box 26)
          - Durer, Albrecht, 1471-1528., 152 (Box 26)
            - Miscellaneous works., 9 (Box 26)
            - Allegory., 10 (Box 26)
            - Portraits., 10 (Box 26)
            - Religious., 94 (Box 26)
              - Miscellaneous subjects., 22 (Box 26)
              - Apocalypse., 9 (Box 26)
              - Engraved Passion., 12 (Box 26)
              - Large Passion., 5 (Box 27)
              - Life of the Virgin., 6 (Box 27)
              - Little Passion., 5 (Box 27)
              - Saints., 17 (Box 27)
              - Virgins and Holy Families., 18 (Box 27)
            - Secular., 29 (Box 27)
          - Ernst, Max, 1891-1919., 7 (Box 27)
          - Fischer, Oskar, 1892-., 3 (Box 28)
          - Graevenitz, Gerhard von, 1934-., 3 (Box 28)
          - Graf, Urs, c.1485-1527/28., 8 (Box 28)
          - Grosz, George, 1893-1959., 4 (Box 28)
          - Gruninger, Johann, active1497., 3 (Box 28)
          - Hausbuch Master, XV C., 8 (Box 28)
          - Heckel, Erich, 1883-1949., 12 (Box 28)
          - Hirschvogel, Augustin, 1503-1553., 20 (Box 28)
          - Holbein, Hans the younger, 1497-1543., 4 (Box 28)
          - Hopfer, Lambert, active 1520-1530., 3 (Box 28)
          - Huber, Wolf, 1490-1553., 5 (Box 28)
          - Kirchner, Ernst, 1880-1938., 21 (Box 28)
          - Koberger, Anton, active 1491., 3 (Box 28)
          - Kohl, Hans, XX C., 3 (Box 29)
          - Kollwitz, Kathe, 1867-1945., 21 (Box 29)
          - Lautensack, Hans Sebald, c.1524-1563., 14 (Box 29)
          - Lemberger, Georg, 1490/95-1540., 3 (Box 29)
          - Marc, Franz, 1880-1911., 6 (Box 29)
          - Master E. S., active 1400-1470., 7 (Box 29)
          - Master H. L., active 1510-c.1533., 6 (Box 29)
          - Master M. Z. (Matthaus Zasinger), XV C., 3 (Box 29)
          - Master of the Rhine, XV C., 3 (Box 29)
          - Meckenem, Israhel van, 1450-1503/17., 7 (Box 29)
          - Molzahn, Johannes, 1892-., 5 (Box 29)
          - Nolde, Emile, 1865-1956., 11 (Box 29)
          - Pechstein, Max, 1881-1955., 3 (Box 30)
          - Richter, G. K. Ludwig, 1823-1884., 3 (Box 30)
          - Schmidt-Rottluff, Karl, 1889-1976., 4 (Box 30)
          - Schongauer, Martin, c.1450-1491., 31 (Box 30)
          - Springinklee, Hans, c.1500-1540., 3 (Box 30)
          - Topp, Arnold, 1887-., 5 (Box 30)
          - Traut, Wolf, actyive 1510-1520., 3 (Box 30)
          - Uhden, Maria, 1892-1918., 5 (Box 30)
          - Wechtlin, Hans, c.1480-c.1520., 5 (Box 30)
          - Wolgemut, Michael, 1434-1519., 3 (Box 30)
    - Holland., 272 (Box 30)
      - Unknown artists., 8 (Box 30)
      - Known artists., 264 (Box 31)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 47 (Box 31)
          - Bloemaert, Abraham, 1564-1651., 1 (Box 31)
          - Bolswert, c.1586-1659., 1 (Box 31)
          - Cornelisz, Jacob van Amsterdam, c.1485-c.1553., 1 (Box 31)
          - Cort, Cornelius, 1533-1578., 1 (Box 31)
          - Coster, Laurens Janszoon, XV C., 1 (Box 31)
          - De Gheyn Jacques, 1565-1629., 2 (Box 31)
          - Delff, William Jacobz, 1580-1638., 2 (Box 31)
          - Ewoutsz, Jan, XVI C., 2 (Box 31)
          - Galle, Philippe, 1537-1612., 2 (Box 31)
          - Grotius, Hugo, 1583-1645., 1 (Box 31)
          - Hoytema, Theo van, 1863-1917., 1 (Box 31)
          - Jongkind, Johann Barthold, 1819-1891., 2 (Box 31)
          - Klooster, Ten, XX C., 1 (Box 31)
          - Kruiningen, Harry van, 1906-., 1 (Box 31)
          - Leck, Bart van der, 1876-1958., 1 (Box 31)
          - Leyden, Lucas van, 1494-1533., 1 (Box 31)
          - Loggan, William, XVII C., 1 (Box 31)
          - Lubbers, Adriaan, 1892-., 1 (Box 31)
          - Matham, Jacob, 1571-1631., 1 (Box 31)
          - Mensinga, J. R., 1924-., 1 (Box 31)
          - Mesquita, Samuel Jessurun de, 1868-1944., 1 (Box 31)
          - Monogrammist, I. A. van Zwolle, XV C?, 1 (Box 31)
          - Muller, Jan, c.1571-1625., 2 (Box 31)
          - Potter, Paulus, 1625-1654., 2 (Box 31)
          - Prikker, Johan Torn, 1868-1932., 1 (Box 31)
          - Reindel, W. G., 1871-., 1 (Box 31)
          - Rogham, Geertruydt, XVII C., 1 (Box 31)
          - Rozendal, W. J., 1899-., 1 (Box 31)
          - Ruysdael, Jacob, 1628-1682., 1 (Box 31)
          - Seghers, Hercules, 1589-1640/5., 1 (Box 31)
          - Sluyters, Jan, 1881-1957., 1 (Box 31)
          - Sok, Ap, 1917-., 1 (Box 31)
          - Van Dalen, Cornelis, 1638-c.1664., 1 (Box 31)
          - Van Leyden, Lucas, 1494-1553., 1 (Box 31)
          - Velde, Willem van de, 1633-1707., 1 (Box 31)
          - Venne, Adriaen van de, 1589-1662., 1 (Box 31)
          - Velde, Esias van de, 1590-1630., 1 (Box 31)
          - Vries, Jan Vriedeman de, 1527-c.1604., 2 (Box 31)
          - Wegner, Toon, 1926-., 1 (Box 31)
        - Individual artists, A-Z., 217 (Box 31)
          - Buytewech, Willem, 1585-1627., 3 (Box 31)
          - Cornelius, Jacob van Oostsanen, 1470-1533., 14 (Box 31)
          - Escher, M. C., 1898-1972., 4 (Box 31)
          - Goltzius, Hendrik, 1558-1616., 13 (Box 31)
          - Heemskerck, Jacoba van, 1876-1923., 5 (Box 31)
          - Lucas van Leyden, 1494-1533., 8 (Box 31)
          - Ostade, Adriaen van, 1610-1685., 4 (Box 32)
          - Rembrandt van Rijn, 1606-1669., 162 (Box 32)
            - Miscellaneous subjects., 34 (Box 32)
            - Life of Christ., 62 (Box 32)
              - Miscellaneous scenes., 28 (Box 32)
              - Christ Preaching., 6 (Box 32)
              - Ecce Homo., 11 (Box 32)
              - Hundred Guilder Print (Christ with the Sick)., 7 (Box 33)
              - Three Crosses., 10 (Box 33)
            - Landscapes., 34 (Box 33)
            - Portraits., 32 (Box 33)
              - Miscellaneous portraits., 25 (Box 33)
              - Self-portraits., 7 (Box 33)
          - Swanvelt, Hermann, c.1620-1690., 3 (Box 34)
          - Van Gogh, Vincent, 1853-1890., 1 (Box 34)
    - Hungary., 11 (Box 34)
      - Known artists., 11 (Box 34)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 11 (Box 34)
          - Kadar, Bela, 1877-1955., 1 (Box 34)
          - Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1895-1946., 2 (Box 34)
          - Rudnay, Gyula, 1878-1957., 2 (Box 34)
          - Semkovits, Jeno, XX C., 2 (Box 34)
          - Silovsky, V., XX C., 1 (Box 34)
          - Thwrocz, Johann de, active 1488, 1 (Box 34)
          - Tordai-Schilling, Oszkar, ?., 1 (Box 34)
          - Vilmos, Aba Norvak, XX C., 1 (Box 34)
    - Italy., 181 (Box 34)
      - Anonymous artists, XIV through XX century., 17 (Box 34)
      - Known artists., 164 (Box 34)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 56 (Box 34)
          - Agostino Veneziano, active 1509-1536., 1 (Box 34)
          - Aldus Manutius, 1450?-1515., 4 (Box 34)
          - Andrea, Zoan, 1475-1505., 2 (Box 34)
          - Andreani, Andrea, 1560-1623., 2 (Box 34)
          - Bellotto, Bernardo, 1720-1780., 2 (Box 34)
          - Bertelli, Luca, active 1560-1582., 1 (Box 34)
          - Bertholomaeus de Zanis, active 1500., 1 (Box 34)
          - Bibiena, Galli da, 1659-1739., 1 (Box 34)
          - Boldini, Jean-Giovanni, 1844-1931., 1 (Box 34)
          - Bonasone, Giulio, 1531-1574., 1 (Box 34)
          - Botticelli, Sandro, 1444-1510., 1 (Box 34)
          - Campigli, Massimo, 1895-1971., 1 (Box 34)
          - Cantarini, Simone, 1612-1648., 1 (Box 34)
          - Carpi, Ugo da, 1479-1532., 3 (Box 34)
          - Castiglione, Giovanni Benedetto, 1616-1670., 1 (Box 34)
          - Clemente, Francesco, 1952-., 1 (Box 34)
          - Coriolano, Bartolomeo, active 1627-1653., 2 (Box 34)
          - Curti, Francesco, XVII C., 1 (Box 34)
          - Fontana, Lucio, 1899-., 1 (Box 34)
          - Giovanni Antonio da Brescia, active 1500-1516., 1 (Box 34)
          - Johannes ex Verona, active 1472., 1 (Box 34)
          - Lasinio, Conte Carlo, c.1757-1839., 1 (Box 34)
          - Manzu, Giacomo, 1908-1991., 1 (Box 34)
          - Master of the Die, XVI C., 1 (Box 34)
          - Montagna, Benedetto, c.1470-1540., 1 (Box 34)
          - Muziano, Girolamo, 1528-1592., 1 (Box 34)
          - Nardo, Simone, active 1505., 1 (Box 34)
          - Pacini, active 1508., 1 (Box 34)
          - Paladino, Mimmo, 1948-., 1 (Box 34)
          - Parmagianino (Francesco Mazzola), 1503-1540., 2 (Box 34)
          - Reni, Guido, 1575-1642., 1 (Box 34)
          - Robetta, Cristofano, 1462-1522., 1 (Box 34)
          - Rosa, Salvator, 1615-1673., 1 (Box 34)
          - Rosex, Nicoletto da Modena, active 1490-1511., 1 (Box 34)
          - Rossi, Lorenzo, active 1497., 1 (Box 34)
          - Sanuto, Giulio, active 1540-1580., 1 (Box 34)
          - Schiavone, Andrea, active 1540-1563., 1 (Box 34)
          - Soffici, Ardengo, 1879-1964., 1 (Box 34)
          - Tiepolo, Giovanni Battista, 1696-1770., 2 (Box 34)
          - Titian (Tizano Vecelli), 1477-1576., 4 (Box 34)
          - Vico, Enea, 1520-1563/7., 1 (Box 34)
          - Vitali, Giancarlo, 1929-., 1 (Box 34)
        - Individual artists, A-Z., 108 (Box 35)
          - Baldini, Baccio, active 1460-1485., 4 (Box 35)
          - Barbari, Jacopo di, c.1450-1516., 4 (Box 35)
          - Bartolozzi, Fran, 1725-1815., 8 (Box 35)
          - Campagnola, Giulio, 1482-1564., 8 (Box 35)
          - Canal, Giovanni Antonio (Canaletto), 1697-1768., 7 (Box 35)
          - Carracci, Annibale, 1560-1609., 2 (Box 35)
          - Mategna, Andrea, 1431-1506., 8 (Box 35)
          - Marini, Marino, 1901-1980., 7 (Box 35)
          - Morandi, Giorgio, 1890-1964., 3 (Box 35)
          - Piranesi, Giovanni Battista, 1720-1778., 28 (Box 35)
          - Pollaiuolo, Antonio, 1433-1498., 3 (Box 35)
          - Raimondi, Marcantonio, 1480-1527., 14 (Box 36)
          - Scolari, Giuseppe, XVI C., 4 (Box 36)
          - Tiepolo, Giovanni Domenico, 1727-1804., 5 (Box 36)
          - Vasi, Giuseppe, 1710-1782., 3 (Box 36)
    - Norway., 38 (Box 36)
      - Known artists., 38 (Box 36)
        - Individual artists., 38 (Box 36)
          - Haagensen, F. H., XX C., 1 (Box 36)
          - Munch, Edvard, 1863-1944., 37 (Box 36)
    - Russia., 55 (Box 36)
      - Known artists., 55 (Box 36)
        - Miscellaneous artists., 10 (Box 36)
          - Bakst, Leon, 1866-1924., 1 (Box 36)
          - Bulkiun, Vladimir, 1886-1917., 2 (Box 36)
          - Dombrowski, Baroness, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 36)
          - Narbut, G., XIX-XX C., 2 (Box 36)
          - Rodchenko, Alexander, 1891-1956., 1 (Box 36)
          - Tchelitchew, Pavel, 1898-1957., 2 (Box 36)
          - Zadkine, Ossip, 1890-., 1 (Box 36)
        - Individual artists., 45 (Box 36)
          - Archipenko, Alexander, 1877-1964., 13 (Box 36)
          - Chagall, Marc, 1887-1985., 12 (Box 36)
          - Kandinsky, Wassily, 1866-1944., 15 (Box 37)
          - Lissitzky, El, 1890-1941., 5 (Box 37)
    - Spain., 89 (Box 37)
      - Unknown artists., 5 (Box 37)
      - Known artists., 84 (Box 37)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 3 (Box 37)
          - Gris, Juan, 1887-1927., 1 (Box 37)
          - Lasansky, Mauricio, 1914-., 1 (Box 37)
          - Ribera, Jusepe de, 1588-1652., 1 (Box 37)
        - Individual artists, A-Z., 81 (Box 37)
          - Dali, Salvador, 1904-1988., 6 (Box 37)
          - Goya, Francisco, 1746-1828., 39 (Box 37)
            - Miscellaneous subjects., 25 (Box 37)
            - Los Caprichos., 14 (Box 37)
          - Miro, Joan, 1893-1983., 6 (Box 37)
          - Morante, Pedro Diaz, XVII C., 3 (Box 37)
          - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973., 27 (Box 38)
    - Sweden., 45 (Box 38)
      - Known artists., 45 (Box 38)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 1 (Box 38)
          - Svanberg, Max, 1911-., 1 (Box 38)
        - Individual artists, A-Z., 44 (Box 38)
          - Haig, Axel H., 1835-1921., 3 (Box 38)
          - Zorn, Anders L., 1860-1920., 41 (Box 38-, Box 39)
    - Switzerland., 25 (Box 39)
      - Unknown artists., 1 (Box 39)
      - Known artists., 24 (Box 39)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 3 (Box 39)
          - Giacometti, Alberto, 1901-1965., 1 (Box 39)
          - Robert, Leopold, 1794-1835., 1 (Box 39)
          - Rossem, Ru van, 1923-., 1 (Box 39)
        - Individual artists, A-Z., 21 (Box 39)
          - Klee, Paul, 1879-1940., 10 (Box 39)
          - Seligmann, Kurt, 1900-1962., 6 (Box 39)
          - Vallotton, Felix, 1865-1925., 5 (Box 39)
    - Latin America., 36 (Box 39)
      - Argentina., 1 (Box 39)
        - Known artists., 1 (Box 39)
          - Nicasio of Argentina, XX C., 1 (Box 39)
      - Cuba., 2 (Box 39)
        - Known artists., 2 (Box 39)
          - Lam, Wilfredo, 1902-1982., 2 (Box 39)
      - Mexico., 33 (Box 39)
        - Unknown artists., 1 (Box 39)
        - Known artists., 32 (Box 39)
          - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 4 (Box 39)
            - Mendez, Leopold, 1903-., 1 (Box 39)
            - Orozco, Jose Clement, 1883-1949., 1 (Box 39)
            - Pas Perez, Gonzalo, XX C., 1 (Box 39)
            - Zuniga, Francisco, c.1913-., 1 (Box 39)
          - Individual artists, A-Z., 28 (Box 39)
            - Posada, Jose Guadalupe, 1851-1913., 24 (Box 39)
            - Charlot, Jean, 1890-., 4 (Box 39)
    - United States., 732 (Box 40)
      - Unknown artists., 17 (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous works., 9 (Box 40)
        - XIX Century., 8 (Box 40)
      - Known artists., 715 (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous artists, A-C., 58 (Box 40)
          - Anderson, Alexander, 1760-1808., 1 (Box 40)
          - Arms, John Taylor, 1887-1953., 3 (Box 40)
          - Avery, Milton, 1893-1965., 1 (Box 40)
          - Bacher, Otto, 1856-1909., 1 (Box 40)
          - Banks, Virginia, XX C., 1 (Box 40)
          - Barnet, Will, 1911-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Baskin, Leonard, 1922-., 4 (Box 40)
          - Bearden, Romare, 1912-1988., 2 (Box 40)
          - Binder, Carl F., XX C., 1 (Box 40)
          - Birch, William, 1755-1834., 1 (Box 40)
          - Bittleman, Arnold, 1933-., 2 (Box 40)
          - Blanch, Arnold, 1896-1968., 2 (Box 40)
          - Blodget, Samuel, XVIII C., 1 (Box 40)
          - Bodmer, Karl, 1809-1893., 1 (Box 40)
          - Bohrod, Aaron, 1907-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Bontecou, Lee, 1931-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Born, Ernest, XX C., 1 (Box 40)
          - Bourgeois, Louise, 1911-., 2 (Box 40)
          - Bowles & Carver, XVIII?, 1 (Box 40)
          - Brook, Alexander, 1898-1980., 2 (Box 40)
          - Brown, Bolton, 1865-1936., 2 (Box 40)
          - Brown, Grafton Tyler, 1841-1918., 1 (Box 40)
          - Browning, Colleen, 1929-., 2 (Box 40)
          - Brussel-Smith, Bernard, XX C., 1 (Box 40)
          - Burchfield, charles, 1893-1967., 1 (Box 40)
          - Butler, Andrew, 1896-., 3 (Box 40)
          - Calder, Alexander, 1898-1976., 2 (Box 40)
          - Canin, Martin, 1927-., 2 (Box 40)
          - Catlin, George, 1796-1872., 2 (Box 40)
          - Chapin, Francis, 1899-1965., 1 (Box 40)
          - Christensen, Dan, 1942-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Clemens, P. L., 1911-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Colman, Charles C., 1840-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Constant, George, 1892-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Cook, Howard, 1901-., 2 (Box 40)
          - Copley, John Singleton, 1738-1815., 1 (Box 40)
          - Corbino, Jan, 1905-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Cornell, Thomas, 1937-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Costigan, John E., 1888-1972., 3 (Box 40)
          - Cottingham, Robert, 1935-., 1 (Box 40)
          - Covey, Arthur, 1877-1960., 1 (Box 40)
          - Cutler, Enid E., XX C., 1 (Box 40)
        - Individual artists, A-C., 148 (Box 41)
          - Albers, Josef, 1888-1976., 6 (Box 41)
          - Audubon, John James, 1785-1851., 9 (Box 41)
          - Bacon, Peggy, 1895-1987., 5 (Box 41)
          - Bellows, George Wesley, 1882-1925., 14 (Box 41)
          - Benson, Frank W., 1862-1951., 7 (Box 41)
          - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1889-1975., 4 (Box 41)
            Includes a folder of miscellaneous prints.
          - Bishop, Isabel, 1902-1988., 4 (Box 41)
          - Bowen, Abel, 1790-1850., 5 (Box 41)
          - Burr, George Elbert, 1859-1939., 6 (Box 41)
          - Cadmus, Paul, 1905-1983., 3 (Box 41)
          - Cassatt, Mary, 1845-1926., 26 (Box 42)
          - Cole, Timothy, 1852-1931., 11 (Box 42)
          - Currier and Ives, XIX C., 42 (Box 42)
          - Curry, John S., 1897-1946., 6 (Box 43)
        - Miscellaneous artists, D-G., 49 (Box 43)
          - Dahlgreen, Charles W., 1864-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Damianakes, Cleon, XX C., 1 (Box 43)
          - Daugherty, James Henry, 1889-1974., 1 (Box 43)
          - Davis, Stuart, 1894-1964., 1 (Box 43)
          - De Martelly, J., 1903-., 2 (Box 43)
          - Diebenkorn, Richard, 1922-1993., 3 (Box 43)
          - Diederich, Hunt, 1884-., 2 (Box 43)
          - Doolittle, Amos, 1754-1832., 3 (Box 43)
          - Dow, Arthur Wesley, 1857-1922., 1 (Box 43)
          - Durand, Asher B., 1796-1886., 2 (Box 43)
          - Durrie, George, 1820-1863., 2 (Box 43)
          - Duveneck, Frank, 1848-1919., 1 (Box 43)
          - Dwight, Mabel, 1876-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Eichenberg, Fritz, 1901-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Estes, Richard, 1936-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Fiene, Ernest, 1894-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Fischl, Eric, 1948-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Fish, Janet, 1938-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Fitzsimmons, James A., 1919-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Ford, Lauren, 1891-., 3 (Box 43)
          - Foster, John, 1648-1681., 1 (Box 43)
          - Frank, Mary, 1933-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1928-., 4 (Box 43)
          - Freeman, Donald, 1908-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Fuchs, Emil, 1866-1929., 1 (Box 43)
          - Gag, Wanda, 1893-1946., 4 (Box 43)
          - Glackens, William J., 1870-1938., 1 (Box 43)
          - Gilliam, Sam, 1933-., 1 (Box 43)
          - Good, Minnetta, XX C., 1 (Box 43)
          - Gorky, Arshile, 1904-1944., 1 (Box 43)
          - Greenwood, John, 1727-1792., 1 (Box 43)
          - Guerrazzi, John B., XIX C.?, 1 (Box 43)
          - Gwathmey, Robert, 1903-., 1 (Box 43)
        - Individual artists, D-G., 47 (Box 43)
          - Dehn, Adolf, 1895-., 4 (Box 43)
          - Dine, Jim, 1935-., 9 (Box 43)
          - Dzubas, Friedel, 1915-., 6 (Box 43)
          - Feininger, Lyonel, 1871-1956., 6 (Box 43)
          - Fenderich, Charles, XIX C., 4 (Box 43)
          - Francis, Sam, 1923-1994., 6 (Box 43)
          - Frasconi, Antonio, 1919-., 5 (Box 43)
          - Ganso, Emil, 1895-1941., 3 (Box 44)
          - Gropper, William, 1897-1977., 4 (Box 44)
        - Miscellaneous artists, H-L., 54 (Box 44)
          - Haas, Richard, 1934-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Haass, Terry, XX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hall, F. G., 1879-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Handforth, T., XX C., 2 (Box 44)
          - Harnett, William M., 1848-1892., 1 (Box 44)
          - Harris, Paul, 1925-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Heaslip, William, 1898-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Heckman, Albert, 1893-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Henderson, Elsie, XX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Higgins, Eugene, 1874-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hill, John, 1812-1879., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hochman, Wallace, XX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hoffman, I. D., 1901-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hoogland, William, 1815-1841., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hoover, Ellisn, 1888-1955., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hornby, Lester G., XIX-XX C., 2 (Box 44)
          - Hunt, Richard, XX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hunt, William Morris, 1824-1879., 1 (Box 44)
          - Hyde, Helen, 1886-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Indiana, Robert, 1928-., 2 (Box 44)
          - Ivins, Florence Wymans, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Jocelin, Nathaniel, 1796-1881., 1 (Box 44)
          - Jones, Joe, 1909-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Jones-Hogu, Barbara J., 1938-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Judd, Donald, 1928-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Kanemitsu, Matsumi, XX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Katz, Alex, 1927-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Kearney, Francis, 1780- after 1833., 2 (Box 44)
          - Kellogg and Comstock, XVII-XIX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1923-., 2 (Box 44)
          - Kircass, W., XIX C.?, 1 (Box 44)
          - Kohn, Misch, 1916-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Kuniyoshi, Yasou, 1893-1953., 2 (Box 44)
          - Lankes, J. J., 1884-., 2 (Box 44)
          - Lassaw, Ibram, 1913-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Lee, Doris, 1905-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Levine, Jack, 1915-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Lewis, James, 1799-1858., 1 (Box 44)
          - Lias, Tom, XX C., 1 (Box 44)
          - Liberman, Alexander, 1912-., 1 (Box 44)
          - Locke, Charles, 1899-., 2 (Box 44)
          - Longacre, James, 1784-1869, 1 (Box 44)
          - Longo, Robert, 1953-., 2 (Box 44)
          - Lozowick, Louis, 1892-1973., 1 (Box 44)
          - Lucioni, Luigi, 1900-., 1 (Box 44)
        - Individual artists., 70 (Box 44)
          - Homer, Winslow, 1836-1910., 11 (Box 44)
          - Hopper, Edward, 1882-1967., 6 (Box 44)
          - Ives, Norman, 1923-., 4 (Box 44)
          - Johns, Jasper, 1930-., 17 (Box 45)
          - Keller, Henry G., 1870-., 3 (Box 45)
          - Kent, Rockwell, 1882-1971., 21 (Box 45)
          - Leslie, Alfred, 1927-., 3 (Box 45)
          - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1923-., 5 (Box 45)
        - Miscellaneous M-Q., 43 (Box 45)
          Includes two folders of miscellaneous clippings, one devoted to Man Ray.
          - MacGilchrist, John, XX C., 1 (Box 45)
          - Marden, Brice, 1938-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Matulka, Jan, 1890-., 1 (Box 45)